http://www.waspbarcode.com/about-us/privacy-policy

Products
Software & Systems:
Inventory ControlInventory Software and Management Systems
Asset ManagementFixed Asset Tracking Software and Systems
Barcode SoftwareBarcode Software for Label Design, Printing, and Tracking
Package TrackingMailroom and Inbound Package Tracking Software
Time & AttendanceTime Clock Software, Hardware, and Systems
Software UpgradesWasp Barcode Software Upgrades
Hardware & Supplies:
Barcode ScannersScanners Designed for Fast and Accurate Tracking
Mobile ComputersMobile Computers for Maximum Rugged Mobility
Barcode PrintersBarcode Printers for All Label Applications and Environments
Labels & SuppliesLabels and Supplies for All Printer Brands
AccessoriesAccessories for Wasp Hardware
View All Wasp Products
Applications
Applications by Use Case:
Mandate Compliance
Applications by Industry:
Support & Training
Frequent Support Options:
Online Support CenterView Our Knowledge Base or Submit a Support Ticket
Instructor-Led TrainingChoose from our Web-Based or On-Site Options
Product TutorialsChapter-Based Video Tutorials Covering Feature-Level Topics
Getting Started TrainingCovers Basic Topics Like Installation and Database Setup
Support PoliciesView Detailed Information About Wasp Support Policies
All Support OptionsSee All of Your Support Options
Other Resources:
Company
Company:
Return Policy
Partners:
WaspLink Partner Program
Find a Partner
Partner Training Center
Become a Partner
Tools:
Software Live Demos
Software Trials
Barcode Generator
QR Code Generator
Learn:
Wasp Privacy Policy
Wasp Barcode Technologies respects the privacy of visitors to its web site.  We place the highest importance on respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers and visitors. Therefore, we have developed and share with you the following privacy policy.
Personal Information
We work to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards. When you register with Wasp, we will ask you for certain personal information.  The information may be combined with other information we have collected from you.  We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interaction on the Wasp site so we can constantly improve the experience you have.
To review Wasp's GDPR Policy, click here.
Uses of Information
When we ask you for information, we will tell you – or it will be clear – what we need to know to fulfill your request and how the information you provide to us will be used. For example, if you request a product demo for download, we will ask you for your name and contact information such as mailing address, phone number, and e-mail address. Wasp may follow up with you after you have downloaded information.
In addition to responding to your request, if you agree, we may use your contact information to send you information about Wasp products or services that might interest you or invite you to participate in a product or service-related survey.
Further, if you agree, Wasp may provide your information to an authorized business partner of Wasp Barcode Technologies for follow up. In this situation, the business partner is providing further assistance for product information and sales fulfillment based on your interest in a Wasp solution.
We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone
Your choice and control
We may use your contact information to keep you informed of Wasp news & events, to tell you about new upgrades, or alert you to other Wasp products we think might interest you. However, if you don't want us to contact you, you can opt-out of future information releases.
You can contact us
If you have privacy-related questions that are not addressed here or wish to contact Wasp about privacy-related issues, please contact us by writing to us at: Wasp Privacy, Wasp Barcode Technologies, 1400 10th Street, Plano, TX 75074.
Wasp provides asset, inventory, and time & attendance systems that are fairly priced, easily implemented, and ready-to-use after installation. Wasp listens to the needs of small business customers because of its passion to help each of those customers succeed.
What do we do?
More about us.
© Copyright 2016, Wasp Barcode Technologies, All rights reserved
Close
Go!
